pasta with olive
potato puree, aged cheddar & crunchy garnishes
$47.00

shrimp dish
summer squash, tomatoes & nasturtium vinaigrette
$76.00

noodle in sweet source
cucumbers, olives, goat cheese & mint
$35.00

steak in love
smoked Butter & Lime
$105.00

desert with bee
burrata cheese, arugula, balsamic vinegar, and basil
$23.00




==========================

» SOUPES & APPETIZERS «
Fried breaded fillet of plaice
served with homemade remoulade and lemon
$22.00

Butter fried fillet of plaice
served with homemade remoulade, lemon and dill
$23.00

Fried fishcake
with homemade remoulade, lemon and dill
$27.00

Chicken salad
with homemade mayonnaise and fried bacon served on toasted white bread
$24.00

Smoked salmon
served with Danish smoked cheese cream and fresh herbs on toasted rye bread
$33.00








» MAIN DISHES «
Meatballs
served on rye bread with homemade pickled red cabbage and pickled cucumbers
$52.00

Creamed chicken and asparagus in crustade
Served with fried bacon and crispy chicken skin
$87.00

Slices of roasted pork
served with rye bread with homemade pickled red cabbage and pickled cucumbers
$56.00

Cod
carefully boiled, served with mustard sauce, boiled potatoes, pickled beetroot, chopped onions, chopped hard boiled eggs and fried bacon
$76.00




PUK Maxi beef sandwich
with homemade mayonnaise and fried bacon served on toasted white bread
$64.00

Herrings with curry
served with gravy, fried onions and pickled cucumbers. Served with French fries and remoulade.
$69.00

Minced beef
served with horseradish, raw onions, capers, pickled beetroots, pickled vegetables and raw egg yolk
$87.00




» DESERTES & DRINKES «
Corned veal brisket
with pickels and horsradish
$22.00

Deep fried camembert
served with blackcurrant jam
$24.00

Prawn cocktail
served with homemade 1000 island-dressing and herb salat
$24.00

Danish blue cheese
from the danis island Bornholm, served with raw onions and raw egg yolk
$24.00

Matured cheese
with fat from pork, raw onions and savoury jelly
$23.00



w100%
p60-0
porelative
bgc


centerline
potatot0
l50%
w1px
h100%
bgc#000
transform:translate(-50%)